

## Jover Gatdula

**Graphic Designer** 

Polomolok, South Cotabato, Philippines +639126329335 · gatdula.jover01@gmail.com

# **Skills** Leadership Ability to Multitask Effective Time Management Communication Adaptability Graphic Design Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Premiere Pro Microsoft PowerPoint Ability to Work Under Pressure Fast Learner Computer Skills **Customer Service** Ability to Work in a Team Communication Skills Microsoft Excel Microsoft Office

## **Profile**

Passionate and experienced Graphic Designer with years of experience working with international clients to create and enhance the aesthetics and function of product designs. Bringing forth the ability to design complex animation elements, edit static images to produce the illusion of motion, and create captivating special effects. Accustomed to working well with others and committed to meeting deadlines and adhering to project guidelines. Offering strong communication skills, and an ability to collaborate and lead as a dynamic and dedicated professional.

## **Employment History**

Senior Graphic Designer, Neon.co.uk, United Kingdom

January 2021 — August 2020

Create engaging and creative graphics to visually represent the company's brand.

#### Graphic Designer, Kings of Neon, Australia

July 2021 — Present

Turn customers' designs and business logos into LED neon using the correct dimensions and specs. Meet client's expectations and deliver the design on time.

### Head of Operations, Van Vliet Digital (NeonDistrict), Netherlands

August 2022 — Present

Oversees the operational activities of a business and ensures that the workforce is productive. Also communicating with the manufacturer to deliver all products to the customers on time.

## **Education**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, Notre Dame of Dadiangas University, General Santos City

March 2014 - March 2020

Polomolok National High School, Polomolok, South Cotabato

June 2009 - March 2012